Ben Browning

Graphic Designer UX/UI Designer

07531 852 200 benjamin.browning@hotmail.co.uk www.benbrowning.me/portfolio.pdf London

Summary

I am currently a UX/UI designer with ClearPeople, based in London. My primary interests in the design world include UI/UX design , branding and typography. Since graduating, I have been lucky enough to largely run my own projects within the agencies I have worked for in both B2B & B2C environments. My personal interests include Running, Poker, Chess & Finance.

Work History

Jul 2019 — Present

UX/UI Designer, ClearPeople Ltd.

My role with ClearPeople as a UX/UI designer is to lead the visual design for their flagship product 'Atlas.' I have also had the opportunity to work as the sole designer for updates on the Bank of England's website, bespoke software design for Korn Ferry & various internal marketing projects.

Oct 2018 — Jul 2019

Graphic Designer, Hirola Group

Hirola Group is a full service creative strategy agency. The company is comprised of a very small team of only 10. Working in collaboration with our account manager, this enabled me to lead my own projects with another designer and a front-end developer. My work consisted primarily of identity design, and UI/UX projects for a very broad range of clients, including the NHS, Walgreens & a number of very interesting start ups.

Nov 2017 — Oct 2018

Jr. Graphic Designer, *RAGS Records*

During my 3rd year of University, I worked part time with a start-up record label — RAGS Records. During this time I developed the brand identity & company website from scratch. I worked closely with the associated artists to develop album artwork and digital marketing assets for social media and live events.

Education

University of the Arts London

BA (hons) Graphic Design

In 2018 I graduated from the University of the Arts London with a BA in Graphic Design. My key achievements during my time here include creating fundraising events for the Camberwell College of Arts graduate exhibition, leading the web design branch of the identity team, and contributing to the development of its branding.